sycamoreeducation.com 2019-05-21

# 5. Sycamore Education clients, including but not limited to schools, colleges, and businesses, will generally collect personal information regarding staff, students, families, and associated parties. This information may include, but not be limited to, employment, tax identification, , financial, emergency contact, medical, insurance, academic, behavioral, and demographic information. It is the responsibility of Sycamore Education clients to utilize the services provided by Sycamore Education in a manner that protects privacy, and that complies with federal, state, and similar regulations unique to the jurisdiction within which the clients operate. 6. Sycamore Education collects personal data about our users when you visit a website hosted by us; apply for a free trial of our products; ask us to contact you, etc., and through the use of cookie technology.

                                 SYCAMORE EDUCATION PRIVACY POLICY
Introduction
1. Your privacy is very important to us. Sycamore Leaf Solutions, LLC (hereafter referred to as Sycamore
Education) is the provider of Sycamore Education, Jcobi Campus, and other web-based management solutions.
This privacy policy applies to any websites and products provided by or associated with Sycamore Education.
We hope that by taking a few minutes to read our Privacy Policy, you will have a better understanding of what
we do with the information you provide to us and how we keep it both private and secure
2. At times, Sycamore Education will collect certain personal information about customers and visitors to
websites hosted by us. Such information will include both identifiable personal data, as well as non-identifiable
personal information. Identifiable personal information will be collected when you sign a contract for service
with us, or use our website for a transaction or subscription service. Non-identifiable information is gathered
automatically when you visit our website or those websites hosted by us, and stored for use in our system.
3. The purpose of this privacy policy is to explain to customers what types of information we will collect and
how that information is used. In most cases, we collect this information to ensure network integrity and that we
continue to provide you with the most relevant content and best possible service that suits your needs. In some
cases, we are required by law to collect personal information about customers. Except where the law requires
otherwise, we undertake to protect the confidentiality of such data.
Confidentiality
4. Sycamore Education respects customer privacy and the privacy of those accessing our website, or those
websites hosted by us. We undertake to protect the confidentiality of our customers and users including all
personal information supplied in the course of contracting with us for services. We undertake not to sell your
personal information to third parties for commercial or marketing purposes.
Collection of Personal Data
5. Sycamore Education clients, including but not limited to schools, colleges, and businesses, will generally
collect personal information regarding staff, students, families, and associated parties. This information may
include, but not be limited to, employment, tax identification, , financial, emergency contact, medical,
insurance, academic, behavioral, and demographic information. It is the responsibility of Sycamore Education
clients to utilize the services provided by Sycamore Education in a manner that protects privacy, and that
complies with federal, state, and similar regulations unique to the jurisdiction within which the clients operate.
6. Sycamore Education collects personal data about our users when you visit a website hosted by us; apply for a
free trial of our products; ask us to contact you, etc., and through the use of cookie technology.

[A cookie is a data file that sits on your computer hardisk. The cookie is placed there by a remote web server
that you have visited using a browser like Netscape or Internet Explorer. It is used to uniquely identify you
during web interactions with a website and contains data parameters that allow the remote HTML server to
keep a record of who you are, and what actions you take at the remote web site. You have the option to disable
the cookie function in your browser, but will be restricted from accessing many sites as a result.]
Use of Personal Data
7. Sycamore Education may log the websites you visit; collect IP addresses and information about your
operating system and the type of browser you use for the purposes of network/system administration, and to
audit the use of our site. This data however will not be used to identify individual users who will at all times
remain anonymous
8. Any information Sycamore Education collects from you through correspondence with us, whether via e-mail,
telephonically or by written letter, will only be used to address the matters within that correspondence. If this
requires referring such correspondence within Sycamore Education or to a third party to ensure customer
service, your personal information will only be disclosed to the point necessary to address your query or
concerns, and will otherwise be kept confidential.
9. Sycamore Education provides a comprehensive Google integration and allows customers to view, manage,
and edit their Google based data through our online web portals. The accessing of this data is through the
OAuth standard and requires the user to explicitly give their consent to Sycamore Education accessing their
personal or organizational data. This Google integration includes but is not limited to the following: retrieval of
personal information to allow for single sign-on into Sycamore Education systems, retrieval and display of
personal and organizational online documents, calendar events, classroom rosters, classroom assignments,
assignment submissions, organizational directories, individual users.
Public Space (Bulletin Boards, Chat Rooms and Third-Party Sites)
10. Any information that customers disclose in a public space, including on or in any bulletin board, news
article, chat room or on any site Sycamore Education may host for you, is available to anyone else who visits
that space. Sycamore Education cannot safeguard any information disclosed there.
Access to Customer Information:
11. The primary goal of Sycamore Education in collecting personal information from our customers is to assist
our customers in managing the information they provide while utilizing our products and services. We have
always safeguarded the confidentiality of information provided to us by our clients and are bound by our
professional standards to continue to maintain this vital aspect of our professional relationship.
The following individuals may have access to some or all of your information:
Employees of the company: Employees who need such information to conclude a transaction or provide
technical support for which the customer has engaged Sycamore Education.
Service providers: Occasionally, service firms may need access to certain information within our databases and
servers. For example. consultants that must have access to certain client records in order to increase the
efficiency of our data processing systems.

Any such information that needs to be disclosed for any business purpose will be considered confidential and
not used for any purpose other than the specific business need. That well-understood business policy of
confidentiality will be reinforced as needed by contractual agreements with any service provider having access
to your data.
Site Linking
12. Sycamore Education’s websites contain many links to sites that belong to third parties. Sycamore Education
cannot be held responsible for any use of your personal information arising from you disclosing personal such
information on third party sites. Sycamore Education cannot protect any information you may disclose on these
sites and recommends that you review the privacy policy statements of those sites you visit.
Reservation of Rights
13. Sycamore Education reserves the right to disclose information about customers where required in good
faith, to do so by law or to exercise our legal rights or defend ourselves against legal claims.
14. Sycamore Education further reserves the right to share information with law enforcement to investigate or
prevent illegal activities being committed over our network.
15. Sycamore Education reserves our rights to disclose your personal information where you have given us
explicit legal written consent to do so.
16. Sycamore Education reserves the right to monitor user and network traffic for site security purposes and
prevent any unauthorized attempts to tamper with our site or cause damage to our property.
17. Sycamore Education reserves the right to make changes to this privacy policy or update it. The most current
version will be posted publicly on Sycamore Education’s websites. Customers and site visitors bear the
responsibility to ensure that they have read the changes or updates as the case may be.
Contact Information:
Sycamore Education
105 E 6th Street, NE 68025
Phone: 866 757 4968
Email: info@sycamoreeducation.com
Last updated: 1/24/18
